<docs>
    <members name="pieceSource">
        <PieceSourceBehaviour>
            <summary>
            The class that handles the behaviour of each <c>GameObject</c> from which the user can drag-and-drop additional pieces for their machine. This script should be added to every such <c>GameObject</c>.
            </summary>
        </PieceSourceBehaviour>
        <piecePrefab>
            <summary>
            The prefab that this particular piece source instantiates when the user touches it.
            </summary>
        </piecePrefab>
        <mainScriptObject>
            <summary>
            The <c>GameObject</c> that stores the central data for the running of the program.
            </summary>
        </mainScriptObject>
        <camLeftButton>
            <summary>
            The <c>GameObject</c> that contains a <c>CameraRotateLeftButtonBehaviour</c> and therefore handles the behaviour of the camera-rotate-left button.
            </summary>
        </camLeftButton>
        <camRightButton>
            <summary>
            The <c>GameObject</c> that contains a <c>CameraRotateRightButtonBehaviour</c> and therefore handles the behaviour of the camera-rotate-right button.
            </summary>
        </camRightButton>
        <pieceLeftButton>
            <summary>
            The <c>GameObject</c> that contains a <c>PieceRotateLeftButtonBehaviour</c> and therefore handles the behaviour of the piece-rotate-left button.
            </summary>
        </pieceLeftButton>
        <pieceRightButton>
            <summary>
            The <c>GameObject</c> that contains a <c>PieceRotateRightButtonBehaviour</c> and therefore handles the behaviour of the piece-rotate-right button.
            </summary>
        </pieceRightButton>
        <OnPointerDown>
            <summary>
            Called when a user begins to touch the piece source <c>GameObject</c>.
            </summary>
            <param name="data">The data concerning the pointer down event.</param>
        </OnPointerDown>
    </members>
    <members name="pieceTrigger">
        <PieceTriggerBehaviour>
            <summary>
            The class that handles the behaviour of each child <c>GameObject</c>, within a machine piece prefab, that contains a collider component. This script should be added to every such <c>GameObject</c>.
            </summary>
        </PieceTriggerBehaviour>
    </members>
</docs>